One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Once there was a man who obtained everything, the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn.
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep.
If we're going to go to an incredible world,
you'll have to be tough.
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner ( • v • )
Freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow.
I'm sure we'll be the first to find One Piece!
Our hearts dream beyond measure...
so let's never wake them up.
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... made it this far.
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us,
and we won't leave anyone behind.
We'll go at it with all our hearts, that's a vow.
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
Adventure in the Ocean Depths!
10 Kilometers Below the Surface!
A creature with no bones... A skeleton with no flesh...
It appears to be my polar opposite.
No one cares!
You're pretty good.
Well, you don't see something like this every day.
You're just calmly sketching it?!
That sounds fine by me,
but do you have a plan, Luffy?
The problem is that we're underwater.
No... No... No...
The problem is how big it is.
Even if we were on the surface, it'd still be just as dangerous.
What's wrong with these people?!
In a situation like this, it's only natural
that everyone would work together to escape!
Turn the rudder! Set a course due south!
Hey, Nami! Head straight for the octopus!
Don't be ridiculous! That octopus is-
Now, now, Nami-san.
I'm here...
for you.
He withstood it! Great job!
It's because of his rehabilitation,
and because Nami's wearing a coat!
This ship is dangerous! I have to save myself!
Something's approaching from behind.
Bro!
That's the ship from before!
Coribou! You guys!
You came back to save me?!
We're gonna save ya, Bro!
Aye!
No!
The soap bubble coating broke!
And that ship was even bigger than the Sunny!
You guys...
They look like jellyfish.
Shut your trap, Roronoa!
It's heading straight for us!
It's way too big!
Gear Thir-
Stop it!
If you perform any big attacks, the soap bubble will break!
Chicken Voyage!
We have to do something! Can't we run away?!
Don't do anything! I'm gonna fight him!
Don't do it! You'll break the soap bubble!
Listen to me! If you want to fight that badly,
I've got an idea.
Right, that's good.
This is the instant Flutter Kick Coating!
An instant diving suit!
If I just left these imbeciles to their own devices,
I'd suffer with them.
What'd you do that for, outsider?!
We should be running away!
Now we'll end up fighting, won't we?!
I've been saying we should run from the start but
that stupid captain of yours doesn't listen, does he?
Would you rather he went wild while
he was still on the ship?!
Alright, get going! As far from the ship as you can!
If you're gonna fight him,
then get away from the ship!
This rope is in the way.
Wait!
You need to keep the lifelines attached!
Otherwise we'll get separated!
Nami-san is worried about me!
You guys! Buy me some time, will you?
I'm gonna take him out with one powerful blow.
I'll just take care of him while you're getting ready.
You'd kill him, so no!
I'm gonna keep that octopus!
It's still coming for us!
Franky...
Rocket Launcher!
You got him!
It's so powerful!
Here comes another arm!
Why is it only attacking us?!
Guard Point!
That was a direct hit!
Are you alright?!
Y-You stopped it!
Well done!
That was amazing, Chopper!
Now we're gonna crash into an underwater mountain!
Mille Fleur...
One Thousand Flowers
Gigantesco Mano!
Gigantic Hand
Enormous hands!
Alright!
Great job, Robin! You saved us!
What a relief...
Even though we're underwater,
I was still able to pull it off for a moment.
Gear Third!
Color of Arms Hardening!
The ocean is... sapping my strength.
Damn octopus, are you trying to stop him
before he lands a single hit?
Blue Walk!
Sanji-san left his soap bubble!
Never mind that! Look at his speed!
He's like a fishman! Amazing!
Running! Running!
I spent two years running from revolting creatures.
Compared to them,
this thing barely even qualifies as a monster.
It's almost cute.
Diable Jambe...
Devil Leg
Bien Cuit...
Well Cooked
Grill Shot!
Secret Three Swords Style Technique...
Crossing of the Six Paths!
A-Amazing...
I couldn't even see his swordplay!
Hey, Zoro, Sanji! You're destroying all of its arms!
Rubber...
Elephant Gun!
He knocked it out!
Just how strong has he become?!
Huh? There's something there!
Huh?
A shark?
Is that shark wearing clothes?
That's a pretty big shark.
What's going on?
They've been sucked into the downflow!
Crap, after them!
We have to stay together!
I don't wanna die here!
Stop messing around!
Hmm? That guy's still here?
Why are you so calm?!
My eyes are spinning! Though I have no eyes.
Keep the yard level! Steer the ship to the left!
We're going to crash into the continental shelf!
Alright!
If we're not careful, the ship will be destroyed!
Whaaaat?!
Don't get thrown off!
Bring the ship to the center of the current!
We're going so fast!
Usopp.
Ow, that hurts.
So I'm still alive?
What's wrong? Why the long faces?
I swear, you really are helpless without me.
It's so cold here!
We can't find Luffy and the others. It looks like we got separated.
What?!
I just hope they haven't been
torn to pieces by a sea monster.
Your imagination is too scary.
Still, we won't find them in this darkness,
no matter how hard we look.
I do not like the darkness...
Do any of you feel like we're being watched?
We're probably at least
7 kilometers down by now.
At this depth, the pressure would even flatten the Shark Submerge like a pancake.
Are we near Fishman Island?
Maybe they're already there?
I think Caimie-chan said
it's 10 kilometers beneath the surface.
We still have to dive another 3 kilometers?!
They're only protected by those small soap bubbles.
Even if they're still alive, they'll run out of air soon!
This is why I told them to keep the lifelines attached!
Crying about it won't get us anywhere.
Let's look for them. I have a light function installed.
Huh?!
Do you mean your eyes?!
Franky...
Nipple Light!
Why would you install lights there?!
These are the deepwater levels. Where the light cannot reach, and ordinary creatures cannot hope to survive.
A true ocean "Underworld".
Let's get out of here!
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
Where did you go?
Come back!
The range of the Sunny Eyes
isn't all that long to begin with.
How disheartening.
This darkness makes it even more depressing.
This isn't getting us anywhere.
What should we do?
We can't slow the ship down,
so make sure you don't miss anything.
A jellyfish! There's a huge jellyfish above us!
It's huge!
It really is massive!
It's sparkling! It looks like a starry night sky!
Its hand entered!
D-Does it want to be friends with me?
You mustn't touch it, Chopper!
It's probably poisonous!
Huh?!
Not good!
Small Coup De Burst!
What?!
The jellyfish was eaten!
The ship seems to have lost some air.
It's better than being eaten, isn't it?
The Coup de Burst is a weapon that uses large amounts of air.
However, we're underwater. Our air is limited!
If we shoot air out, the soap bubble shrinks!
The fish that attacked the jellyfish went belly up!
Neurotoxin, as I suspected.
The deep sea is so scary! And dark.
And there are so many fish
with white eyes. They're creepy!
The deep sea is a world of darkness. Thus,
the eyes of many creatures here have degenerated.
Oh, so they can't see very well?
Stupid! Try to come over here!
What? How can I see with no eyes, you ask?
On the other hand,
some creatures will have highly evolved eyes.
The answer is...
It's a secret!
What are you doing over there, all by yourself?
No need to worry. I am quite used to solitude.
Luffy, Zoro, Sanji!
Where did you go?
Hmm?
These ropes...
Everyone?
Huh?
Do you know what happened to that pirate fellow?
Oh yeah, he was here too.
I'd completely forgotten.
Where did he go?
I haven't seen him since we reached the deep sea.
Maybe he got thrown off in the downflow?
That could be.
His hands and legs were bound, after all.
He couldn't hold on to anything.
No, you see...
It seems his ropes came off. Look.
T-Then he's still onboard?
Where could he be?!
He could be lurking inside the ship somewhere.
If you want me to lurk around then maybe I should.
Like in the ladies' quarters?
Damn... So we can't even
drop our guard on our ship?
Don't worry. He's not all that strong, anyway.
This is great!
The monster trio who fought the Kraken
have gone missing!
They're dead for sure after getting lost down here in such small bubbles!
It's a shame I couldn't take Straw Hat's head, but...
as long as I collect
the heads of everyone on this ship,
that should be more than enough proof
that Straw Hat is dead!
However, don't be hasty, Caribou!
You mustn't act too quickly!
If you kill them now there will be nobody to sail the ship.
These guys are skilled at navigating the sea.
But the moment when we reach Fishman Island...
will be their last!
Here he is!
Dammit!
I screwed up!
Now we'll be safe.
How did he get inside this small barrel?
We were careless. We might have been in trouble
if this guy wasn't such an idiot.
His body lost its form and became a muddy substance.
He's a devil fruit user, no doubt about it.
What's more, he's a Logia.
He took our attacks on purpose earlier, and pretended he'd been captured.
Hey! Please let me out, master!
Master with the speedo! I'll be your servant!
What is it, Chopper?
I don't know, it got really hot all of a sudden.
I can't handle heat.
So hot! What's going on?!
Huh, what's this? Smoke?
It's blocking our view!
Smoke from the ocean floor? How?
This is...
Could it be?!
Hydrothermal deposits!
Huh?
This is a field of underwater volcanoes!
Look! You can see that they were recently active.
We have to get out of here!
If one of them erupts, we'll die instantly!
Hot... so hot!
Something's coming after us!
A carnivorous tube worm!
Faceless crabs!
I have no idea what that is!
Small...
Coup de Burst!
The deep sea is scary!
There's no way Luffy and the others could survive down here.
I'm so sad. We finally met after two years,
and now...
Don't be ridiculous! They won't die that easily!
We used one Coup de Burst after another... There isn't much air left.
What's that? It's so bright!
Maybe it's Fishman Island!
Maybe Luffy and the others are there!
We haven't dived down 3 kilometers yet.
W-h-o a-r-e y-o-u?
Hey! What are you sending those signals with?!
Can you see anything?
It's still too bright.
Oh no!
It's an angler! It tricked us!
We've been caught by a deep sea hunter!
This is not good!
That was close!
It lured us right into its trap! Can we get away?
What is it now?!
A-A human?!
What is that?!
A sea monster with the shape of a human!
A Sea Bonze!
He's gonna capsize the ship!
The fish?!
Hey! Angler! You can't do that!
No eating ships!
How many times do I hafta tell ya?
Captain Vander Decken's gonna yell at ya!
D-Did he just save us?
L-Let's get out of here! Who cares what happened?
Both of them are monsters!
Dead men tell no tales and know no greed.
Is that...
...me?
In this country so black that even crows don't fly,
What is that?!
the dead need no jewels upon their fingers.
They can't even see their own regrets in the darkness.
Search for it! Search for it!
All sunken treasure belongs to me!
I am the world's richest man, Captain Vander Decken!
It can't be...
Even at the bottom of the sea?!
Nooooooooooo!
It's a ghost ship!
Why are you getting scared?!
T-That is a real one! Look at the sail!
That is the legendary Flying Dutchman!
It's a ship that shouldn't exist in this world!
There is a tale from many centuries ago.
One day, during a storm,
the captain of a ship suddenly went insane.
He started throwing his crewmates
into the stormy sea, killing them one after another.
He even spat in the face of God!
The name of that captain was Vander Decken!
And the name of the ship was The Flying Dutchman!
He incurred the wrath of God,
and now he's cursed to drift through the seas,
tortured for all eternity!
The ship we see before us is the very same cursed ship of Captain Vander Decken!
Angler! Wadatsumi! If you eat the ship, I won't be able to take their treasure!
Smash it!
Gotcha!
Wah! The Sea Bonze...
So it's an enemy after all!
Franky! Use the Coup de Burst!
I can't! We're all out of fuel!
We have to refill the cola in the energy room!
The Kraken?!
The beast of the North Pole, the Kraken.
Ya bastard!
Hey, that's enough!
Cut it out!
You did great!
Heeeey!
Luffy! Zoro, Sanji!
I'm so glad you're alive!
Nami-swan! Robin-chwan!
We've been looking for you guys!
They sure caused us a lot of trouble...
Getting separated from us...
Hey! Wake up, Wadatsumi!
Time for a rematch! Get them!
Me and Sanji's bubbles burst, so we got into Zoro's.
We almost died!
Don't make us worry so much!
Finally some space! Being at home really is the best!
Luffy! I was so worried!
I'm impressed by your vitality!
Unbelievable! You actually tamed it?!
That monstrous octopus?!
That's right! I'm using him to travel like a pro!
Isn't that right, Surume?
Why'd you give him a squid name?!
He isn't exactly "pulling" the ship though.
I just hope he's careful that he doesn't crush us.
What's going on?
Huh?!
This is bad, Captain Vander Decken!
Not good! The underwater volcanoes...
are erupting!